KIRBY MEKLER

<u>kirbymekler@gmail.com</u> I 786-877-5558 LinkedIn: <u>Kirby Mekler</u> I Github: <u>kmekler</u>

Summary

Kirby is a full stack web developer with an eye for design and a love of learning. When interacting with clients, Kirby has a unique perspective due to her background in digital marketing, entertainment and event management. Kirby thrives when faced with a challenge, and is excited to grow and test her abilities in a new position.

Expertise

Website optimization (speed and usability)

E-commerce

Web content management

- Agile development methodologies
- Collaboration
- Communication

Technology

PHP, Laravel, Python, Ruby, Version Control on GitHub, AWS (CloudSearch, S3), Twitter Bootstrap, JavaScript, Symfony, Rails, MySQL, jQuery, HTML, SASS, LESS, CSS, Agile Development

Experience

LabRoots

Junior Developer (January 2016-April 2016)

- · Built out a new press room section
- Revamped team page
- · Fixed bugs throughout site
- Environment: PHP, MySQL, Symfony, HTML5, SASS, Git

Clique Media / Who What Wear

Junior Developer (March 2015-November 2015)

- Integrated both standard and custom data feeds into Python-based shop application
- Developed front-end revamp of shop platform, and contributed front end editorial changes
- Built out new features for admin, including the ability to add custom products and a processing dashboard
- Developed new search page for publishing platform
- Tackled bugs in shop, editorial and publishing
- Contributed to publishing, editorial, shop and data applications for "Who What Wear", "Byrdie" and "MyDomaine"
- · Environment: PHP, Laravel, Python, MySQL, HTML5, LESS, Git

HelloSociety

Influencer Representative (March 2014-June 2014)

- Built and maintained relationships with over 100 HelloSociety Pinterest Influencers
- Conducted blogger outreach and recruitment
- Monitored Influencer activity and dedicated campaigns
- Operated HelloSociety house Pinterest accounts
- Planned Influencer meet-ups

Education

General Assembly (September 2014-December 2014) Web Development Immersive

University of Central Florida (August 2007-May 2011) Bachelor of Science in Event Management